<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DemoLivescore</string>
    <string name="title_scores">Scores</string>
    <string name="title_favorites">Standing</string>
    <string name="title_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="title_logo">Logo</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search">SearchActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail_match">DetailMatchActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="detail_news">Paul Scholes claimed Paul Pogba will still be doing \"this stupid stuff" at the age of 35 after the Manchester United midfielder disappointed against Atalanta.

Pogba was restored to the starting line-up for Tuesday's Champions League game after missing the 3-0 Premier League win at Tottenham due to suspension.

However, the France international was substituted with 69 minutes gone despite United trailing 2-1 to the home side after a frustrating performance.

Pogba gave up the ball 13 times in the United midfield, including once when he dawdled on the ball on the edge of his own box and had a pass cut out, with Eric Bailly scrambling to deny Duvan Zapata a clear shot at goal.

United in the end salvaged a 2-2 draw, with Cristiano Ronaldo, who had earlier cancelled out Josip Ilicic's opener, blasting home a second in the 91st minute after Zapata's goal looked to have given Atalanta the win.

Pogba leads the assists charts in the 2021-22 Premier League with seven, but his inconsistent form continues to be a concern for United, who could see the World Cup winner leave on a free transfer next year if he does not sign a new contract.</string>
</resources>